pdfmage.org 2018-11-30

# PDF Mage | A browser extension to save pages as PDF

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### Collection of personal information

When visiting PDF Mage webpage, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links to third party websites

Our website may contain links to other websites that may interest you. However, once you have used one of these links to leave our site, we have no control over content and activity of any third party websites. And we cannot ensure the privacy and protection of your personal information. Therefore, if you are concerned about the safety of your personal information you should always consult privacy policies of the websites you are visiting. If a website does not provide any privacy policy you should exercise extreme caution while visiting this site.

### Google Adsense

This site uses Google Adsense. Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. These cookies are used to track visitors' activity and collect anonymous information based on visits to this and other sites. Such tracking mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies available at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. If you do not wish to have Google track your activity via cookies you can opt out of Google cookies by visiting the URL given above. Other Third Party advertisers may also use cookies to track users' activities for various reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies.

### Certain exceptional disclosures

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process.

### Personal data

PDF Mage does not require any personal data (email addresses, names, etc.) to be provided by users. However, when using our PDF generation service, you may choose to save some personal data from web pages inside PDF files. As the generated PDF files are hosted at PDF Mage servers, we try our best to ensure that the data inside these files is unavailable to anyone but the person who initiated the conversion. We do not harvest any personal data we get in any way and do not share it with third parties. The generated PDF files are only stored at our servers for 10 minutes aftre creation, and after that they are pemanently deleted and become inaccessible to anyone.

The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). As the controller, PDF Mage has implemented various technical and organizational measures to ensure the most complete protection of personal data processed through our services. However, Internet-based data transmissions may in principle have security gaps, so absolute protection may not be guaranteed. For this reason, every data subject is free to anonymize any data sent to PDF Mage, or to completely remove any personal personal information from it.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure the information we collect online.
